鸡尾酒
伙计
Dude.
怎么回事
What's up with that, huh?
生意不做了吗
Yo, why's the deal walking out the door, man?
潘尼亚不感兴趣
Pena ain't interested in meet-and-greet.
至少今天是
Not today anyway.
所以他就这么走了
So he just gonna walk out the door like that?
你告诉他我有新枪货源了吗
Did you tell him I got new heaters with no heads on 'em?
和这个没关系
Got nothing to do with that.
他有别的事
He's just got something else going on.
什么事
Like what?
入会日
Initiation Day.
真的吗  因为入会日
Really, Initiation Day?
揍几个小子用多长时间
How long does it take to beat up some boys?
对潘尼亚来说  不只是这样
To Pena, it's more than that.
监狱让他比以前更疯狂了
Prison made him even crazier than he was.
什么意思
Okay. What does that mean?
他想让他的跟班们
It means that he wants his whole crew to be
都像他一样坏透了才行
straight up evil... just like him.
听着  我看到了潘尼亚
Listen, I got long eyes on Pena
和三个西班牙裔男性
and three male Hispanics,
要走了  上了一辆银色的雪佛兰
ready for action, hopping in a silver Caprice.
-看不清车牌...  -你干嘛
- Can't make the plates out... - What you on about, homey?
你突然过来吓我一跳
Hell you all over me, man? Huh?
你知道我来这里干嘛
You know what I came here to do.
你搞什么
What you playin' for, G?
你想来接近老大  但今天不行
You trying to get to jefe, but it's not happening today.
所以你最好别在这儿乱晃
So it's best you keep on moving.
-会死是吗  -会死
- It's dead, huh? - It's dead.
听着  伙计...
Listen, bro...
我只是做生意的
I'm just a businessman.
好吗  我不是来干别的
A'ight? I ain't come here for all that.
让潘尼亚知道
On God. Let Pena know,
他什么时候准备好了都可以来找我
whenever he ready to do business, I'm ready.
老大  有情况
Boss, we have a situation.
好  都听着
Yo- All right, listen up.
阿特沃特的枪支生意黄了
Atwater's gun lead went south,
但我们有新消息
but we got something else.
有两个潜在青少年罪犯
There's two wanna-be gangbangers out in the wind
准备干坏事
looking to do something stupid.
今天是三街王者帮的入会日
It's initiation day for the Three Corner Kings.
潘尼亚回来当老大真不是好事
Ah, man, with Pena back in charge that's not good.
他出来才三个月
He's only been on the streets for three months.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
就犯下了六桩谋杀案
He's already good for six homicides.
那我们要快点把那些小子拉出来
All right, so let's get these kids off the street fast.
有需要的话就造个指控出来
Invent a charge if you have to.
把他抓回来再说
Just bring him in.
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   Lynn_宁   H小欠
怎么
Yeah?
通缉这辆车
Get a BOLO out on that car.
新型银色雪佛兰
Late-model silver Caprice.
翻译     小萝莉   西之   圈圈
阿特沃特看到了一部分车牌
That's the partial plate Atwater got.
警号5021E  所有小组注意
5021 Eddie, all units be on the lookout
寻找一辆新型银色雪佛兰
for a late-model silver Caprice.
校对     圈圈
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
-车在哪  -不在这里
- Where's the car? - It's not here.
调度部说他们十分钟前在这个街区
Dispatch said they picked up a silver Caprice
后期     8T
看到了一辆银色雪佛兰
on this block ten minutes ago.
调度部确认这就是确切地址
Dispatch confirmed this is the right address.
总监     圈圈
伙计们
Guys...
新的轮胎印
Fresh tire tracks.
看起来他们走得很匆忙
Looks like they left in a hurry.
大家看看这个
Guys, check this out.
海莉
Hailey...
老天
Oh, my God.
死了
Dead.
见鬼的入会
That's one hell of an initiation.
什么禽兽会干这种事
What kind of animal does something like this?
什么禽兽会让人干这种事
What kind of animal makes someone do this?
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十五集
看起来他们把她拖进来  强奸了她
Looks like they dragged her inside, raped her.
这是潘尼亚新的入会仪式吗
This is Pena's new initiation ritual,
奸杀女人
rape and kill women?
对  控制人  控制地盘
Yeah, control the people, control the territory.
她还是个孩子
She's just a kid.
不会超过17岁
She can't be 17.
去找线人  拿到这两个菜鸟的名字
Right. Talk to your CI, get the names of those two pledges.
要快
Fast.
老大
Hey, boss.
巡逻队在十个街区外看到了那辆雪佛兰
So patrol located the Caprice about ten blocks away
-但已经被烧了  -车在谁的名下
- but it's been torched. - Who's it registered to?
迈克尔·兰德瑞  54岁  黑人男性
A Michael Landry. Male, black, 54.
上周报警说车被偷了
It was reported stolen last week.
在门边发现了这个
Found this by the door.
一条手链
Charm bracelet.
汉克
Hank.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for doing this.
伙计们  这是斯科特·哈特警探
Guys, this is Detective Scott Hart.
-中区重案组的  -金
- Area Central Homicide. - Kim.
是个好警察
Good police.
他这么说是因为我兄弟
He's saying that 'cause my brother
刚刚当上巡逻队长
just turned Chief of Patrol.
这个案子我们会一起合作
Well, we're working together on this.
-金  你配合斯科特  -好的
- Kim, you partner up with Scott. - Great.
这是我这个月见到的第五个了
Fifth one I've seen this month.
好
Okay.
我线人电话
That was my CI.
他发誓他不认识他们
He swears he can't ID the two pledges.
-你相信他吗  -这不重要
- You believe him? - Doesn't matter.
他没把他们供出来
He's not giving them up.
法医报告出来了
I got the M.E. Report.
受害者遭到了强奸  然后被勒死
The DOA was raped, then strangled to death.
检测到强奸犯的DNA了吗
Any third-party DNA?
没有  他们戴了安全套
No, they were wearing condoms.
他们在受害者体内
They found traces of spermicide
发现了杀精剂
inside the Jane Doe.
受害人名叫丹尼奥拉·里奥斯
Her name's Daniella Rios.
你怎么知道的
Yeah? How do you know?
我查了一下当地的舞蹈团体
I was researching local dance groups.
她穿的衣服像跳舞的
She looked like she was wearing a dance uniform,
手上还戴着舞蹈手链
and there was a dance charm on her bracelet.
乡村舞蹈  是课后兴趣小组
Village Dance, it's an after-school program
给高危青少年组建的  衣服是统一的
for at-risk teens. Uniform's the same.
我用她名字去查一下住址
I'll run her name, get an address.
-已经查了  -去和家属谈谈
- I already did. - So go talk to the family.
没错  我是安娜·里奥斯  什么事
Yes, I'm Ana Rios. What's this about?
你要不要坐下
Would you like to take a seat?
怎么回事  你们为什么来找我
What happened? Why are you here?
我很遗憾告诉你这件事  女士  但是
I'm sorry to tell you this, ma'am, but
我们在一间废弃公寓中找到了一名年轻女子的尸体
we found a young girl's body inside an abandoned apartment.
我们觉得可能是你的女儿  丹尼奥拉
And we think it might be your daughter, Daniella.
丹尼
Danni?
什么
What?
你...
Are you...
你是说她...她死了吗
Are you saying she's--she's dead?
这是她吗
Is this her?
不  不  我的孩子
No, no. Mi hija.
里奥太太  我们很遗憾
Mrs. Rio, we are so sorry for your loss.
我们知道这很艰难  里奥斯太太
I know this is hard, Mrs. Rios,
但现在时间很紧迫
but the clock is ticking.
你的女儿有什么麻烦吗
Was your daughter in any trouble?
有人骚扰她吗
Was anyone bothering her?
不  从来没有
No. Never.
-她...人很好  -好吧
- She was...sweet. - Yeah.
她明年就要上大学了
She was going to college next year.
我...我要回家
I--I need to go home.
我知道  我知道  我明白
I know, I know, I understand.
我们会派巡逻车送你回家  好吗
And we're gonna get you a patrol car home, okay?
我在那间废弃的公寓中发现了这条手链
I found this bracelet at the abandoned apartment.
这是丹尼奥拉的  我觉得
It was Daniella's, and I thought
你也许会想要这个
you might want to keep it.
不  那不是丹尼的手链
No, that's not Danni's bracelet.
-你确定吗  -我确定
- Are--are you sure? - I'm positive.
这是她最好的朋友  蒂娜的
It belonged to her best friend, Tina.
丹尼在她成人礼的时候给她的
Danni gave it to her for her quinceanera.
你觉得蒂娜当时也在那个废弃的公寓吗
You think Tina was at the abandoned house too?
请坐
Have a seat there.
蒂娜  我们想谈谈你朋友丹尼的事
Tina, we want to talk to you about your friend Danni.
你最后一次看到她是什么时候
When's the last time you saw her?
丹尼的妈妈
You know, Danni's mom,
说这条手链是丹尼给你的
she said that Danni gave you this bracelet
15岁生日礼物
for your 15th birthday.
是吗
Yeah?
我们在丹尼被杀的房中发现了这条手链
We found the bracelet inside the house Danni was killed.
-你当时在场吗  -不
- Were you there? - No.
那手链怎么会出现在那里
Then how did the bracelet get in there?
蒂娜  他们也伤害了你  是吗
Oh, Tina, they hurt you, too, didn't they?
这些淤青看起来很严重
Look, those bruises look really bad.
我送你去医院检查一下吧
Can I get you to the hospital and get you checked out?
如果你被侵犯了  我们必须
If you were assaulted, it's important
-对你做强奸检查  -我说了不要
- that we do a rape kit. - I said no.
我可以给你看一些照片
I can show you some photos.
你可以指认那些伤害你
So you can help identify the guy that hurt you
-并杀死丹尼的人  -我只想回家
- and killed Danni. - I just want to go home.
你可以回家  你得先...
Look, you can go home after--
嗯  我觉得这是个好主意
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
没关系
That's fine.
不如你先回家
Why don't you go home,
好好休息  等你准备好开口
you take a rest, and when you're ready to talk,
打电话给我
call me.
走吧
Okay. Come on.
听说那个叫蒂娜的女孩也被侵犯了
I heard that Tina girl got assaulted too?
是的  她没明说  但是很明显
Yeah. I mean, she didn't say that, but it's pretty obvious.
-可怜的孩子吓坏了  -情有可原
- Poor kid's terrified. - I don't blame her.
太可怕了
It's just horrible.
是啊
Yeah.
怎么了
What's up?
去年我姐姐也经历了这种事
I dealt with this last year with my sister.
她被人下药  遭到强奸
She got drugged and raped.
嗯  我听说了
Yeah, I heard.
但你们还是找到了侵犯者  对吧
You guys hooked the offender though, right?
我们找到了侵犯者
Oh, we hooked the offenders, yeah.
我们逮捕了他们
We arrested them.
但是那个法官不置可否
But the judge, he whiffed.
他只是轻轻拍了拍他的屁股说"以后别这样了"
He just smacked him on the ass and said, "Don't do it again."
三年  几年出来  一年吗
Three years. I mean, out in what? One?
-我很遗憾  -我也是
- I'm sorry. - Me too.
案子怎么样了
What's going on with the case?
鲁塞克和我一直在看三号录音带
Ruzek and I have been going over the Title 3 wiretaps but--
他说凶案当晚有很多通讯
But he said there's a lot of chatter the night of the murder
但都好像是加密的
but it's all in code or something?
全是数字  没有单词或字母
Mm-hmm. All numbers, no words or letters.
有发现
Got something.
太好了
Good.
王者帮密码破译
我找过帮派情报部
All right, so I talked to Gang Intel.
他们帮我们破译了密码
They helped me crack the code.
每个字母就是一个数字
Each letter's a number.
他们将字母表分成奇数和偶数两部分
They split the alphabet in half, evens and odds
增大破译难度  A是1  B是3
to make it confusing so A is 1, B is 3.
然后到第13个数字又清零翻转
Then by the 13th letter, it flips.
N是2  O是4  以此类推
N is 2, O is 4, so on and so forth.
我们可以破译出这些
Anyway, we came up with this.
这句话的意思是"我们杀了一个女孩"
"Matamos a una." It means "We killed one girl."
这是米格尔·斯拉泽发来的信息
That was an incoming text sent by Miguel Salazar.
一分钟后  爱德华多·瓦格斯又发来
A minute later, another incoming text was sent
一条信息
from Eduardo Vargas.
这句话的意思是"另一个逃走了"
"La otra escapo." It means "The other escaped."
这两个笨蛋都用自己的手机
Both of these idiots, they used their own phones.
这些信息都是发到一个一次性手机上
Texts were sent to a burner phone that we think
我们认为是潘尼亚的
is owned by Pena.
搜过他们的名字了吗
You run their names?
都十八岁  劣迹斑斑
Both are 18, both have impressive juvie sheets.
定位他们的手机  把他们抓起来
Ping their phones, grab them up.
这间开着
Hey, this is open.
芝加哥警局  举起手来
Chicago PD, hands up.
发现两具尸体
Got two bodies.
好吧  这...
Hmm, okay, that's...
这算是惩罚强奸犯的一种方式吧
That's one way to take care of rapists.
开什么玩笑  他们被阉割了
You gotta be kidding me. They cut 'em off.
看来有人在我们之前找到了我们的目标
Looks like someone got to our targets before we did.
这个人可是动真格的
Yeah, and that someone was not playing either.
我们听说了
Yeah, we heard about it.
-有目击证人吗  -没有  长官
- So any witnesses? - No, sir, nothing.
确认这里就是米格尔和爱德华多的住所
We confirmed this is where Miguel and Eduardo live.
我们朋友住在那里
Our friends live in that house.
我们只想知道他们好不好
We just want to know if they're okay.
-这是我们的权利  -抱歉  让他们进来
- It's our legal right. - I'm sorry, let them in.
是你们的权利是吧
It's your legal right, huh?
你从哪学来的  法学院吗
Where'd you learn that, law school?
我们只想知道到底怎么回事
We just want to know what happened.
我很乐意说  和潘尼亚说
I'm happy to talk about it... with Pena.
你告诉他  汉克·博伊特一小时内要见到他
You tell him Hank Voight wants to see him in one hour.
行  行
All right. All right.
好吧  他们死了
Okay, they're dead.
那是谁杀的
So who did the murders?
我正希望你能告诉我呢
Well, I was hoping you could tell me.
这些小子的死法
I mean, the way these kids were killed
显然是私人恩怨
it was obviously personal.
某个男性器官被割掉了
Certain male body parts were severed.
-你是说他们...  -我是这个意思
- What you sayin'? That they... - That's what I'm saying.
狠啊
Damn.
我可不想闹到这步  是吧
I'd hate to go out like that, huh?
-发现这些小子告密了吗  -不是
- Caught these kids snitching? - Nah.
他们也没什么可告的密
They didn't know enough to snitch.
那是你和谁开战了吗
Well, you're at war with someone?
现在不搞战争了  哥们
We don't do wars, socio.
对生意不好
It's bad for business.
是啊  可是
Yeah, but, uh,
可是奸杀小姑娘
but raping and killing little girls,
-就好了吗  -我没这么说
- that's good? - I didn't say that.
不过如果你想统治一个街区或地盘
But if you want to own a neighborhood or a territory,
你就得碾碎他们的灵魂
you got to break its soul first.
联系你的线人  重新谈那个交易
Call your CI, get that deal back on track.
我想灭了这个王八蛋
I want to bury this son of a bitch.
不是
No.
我要碾碎他的灵魂
I want to break his soul.
我们和线人  帮派情报都谈过了
Yo, yo, so we talked to CIs, Gang Intel, bangers.
没人和这个帮派有冲突
There are no conflicts with the King crew,
至少现在没有
at least not right now.
也就是说这两个混蛋强奸犯
Which means these two punk rapists--
抱歉  被害人
Sorry, victims,
可能是被某个和丹尼奥拉
were probably killed by somebody
和蒂娜有关系的人杀死的
connected to Daniella or Tina.
-她们才是受害人 -确实有种复仇的意思
- You know, the real victims. - Sure feels like revenge.
看起来也像
Yeah, looked like it too.
那重新聚焦到这家人身上
Okay, so circle back with the family.
肯定有个什么哥哥  叔叔
There's got to be a brother, an uncle,
某个有能耐做这种事的人
somebody out there capable of doing this.
真希望我姐姐也能有个这样的亲戚
I wish my sister had someone like that in her life.
这样事情就简单多了
Would have made things a lot easier.
我明白
I get it.
你就保持头脑清醒  好吗
Just keep your head straight, okay?
还得破双尸案呢
Got a double homicide to clear.
我说了第十遍了  我谁都没说好吗
For the tenth time, I didn't tell anyone, okay?
求你们了别来烦我
So please, leave me alone.
我只想向前看  忘了这件事
I just want to move on and forget this ever happened.
我知道  但没这么容易
Yeah, I know, but it's not that easy.
因为伤害你的那两个人已经死了
Because the two men who hurt you are dead.
有人杀了他们
Someone killed them.
蒂娜  只有你知道到底发生了什么
Tina, you are the only one who knows what happened.
你看见了这两个混蛋的脸
You saw the faces of these two punks.
所以要么是你做的
So either you did it
要么是你找人做的
or they told somebody and they did it.
我没杀他们
I didn't kill them.
我绝对不会的  太可笑了
Okay? I would never. That's--that's ridiculous.
我相信你  真的
I believe you. I do.
但我认为你可能告诉了谁
But I think maybe you told someone.
-比如你妈妈  -我妈
- Like your mom? - My mom?
-对  -得了吧
- Sure. - Please.
她自己麻烦事就够多了  相信我
She's got enough problems, trust me.
这照片挺甜蜜啊  他是谁
That's a sweet picture. Who is that?
那是但丁  我男友
That's Dante. My boyfriend.
你没告诉但丁吗
You didn't tell Dante?
没有  不能说
No. No way.
为什么  他会打你吗
Why? Is he violent?
因为我爱他
Because I love him.
而我绝对不希望他知道我被人...
And I would never want him to know that someone--
我理解
I understand that.
但我们需要和但丁谈谈
But we do need to talk to Dante.
你能告诉我们他在哪吗
Could you tell us where he is?
他在J&P金属厂上班
At J&P Metals. He works there.
别告诉他我的事
Don't tell him what happened.
求你了  不然他以后都不会正眼看我了
Please, he'd never look at me the same.
-但丁·席尔瓦  -我们是芝加哥警察
- Dante Silva? - Chicago PD.
我们想和你谈谈你女友蒂娜的事
We want to talk to you about your girlfriend, Tina.
怎么了  她出什么事了吗
Why? Something happen to her?
-是  昨天她...  -她朋友丹尼
- Yes, yesterday she was... - Her best friend, Danni,
被人强奸并杀害了
was sexually assaulted, murdered.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
那和蒂娜有什么关系
What's that got to do with Tina?
杀害丹尼的那两个人  后来也死了
The two guys that killed Danni, they wound up dead.
凶手意图很明确  割下了他们的  你懂的
Killer made a real statement by cutting off their--you know.
该
Good.
要我说  就该全城公告这两个混蛋
Ask me, we should tell the whole city what happened
遭遇了什么  得让其他的混蛋强奸犯知道
to those dudes and that other bitch-ass rapist, too.
什么其他的强奸犯
What other bitch-ass rapist?
某个看门员
Some janitor.
湖边高中
Lakeside High.
听说他强奸过女生
Heard he raped a girl.
他也被人报复了
He got dealt with too.
我就知道这些
That's all I know.
-我得回去忙了  -好
- I got to get back to work. - Yeah.
你们  刚才都有点吓着我了
You guys... You guys scared me.
闪着个警徽就进来了
Coming in with those badges,
我还以为蒂娜出什么事了呢
I thought something bad happened to Tina.
没有
No.
要么他是史上最优秀的演员
Either he's the best actor alive
要么他完全不知道蒂娜被强奸了
or he has no clue Tina got raped.
我们找到被害人马克·威特莫
We found the DOA, Mark Whitmore,
是在离他在威尔米特住所两街区外的垃圾箱里
in a garbage bin two blocks from his house in Wilmette.
胸口中枪  而且被阉割了
Gunshot wound to the chest and he'd been castrated.
威尔米特  可是他在小村镇上班吧
Wilmette, but he works in Little Village, right?
-湖边高中  -对
- Lakeside High? - Yeah.
他是个维护工
He was a maintenance worker.
他有性侵前科吗
Did he have any sexual assault priors?
两起  还有不少吓人的传闻
Two. Lot of nasty rumors swirling around as well.
-为什么  -因为我们在小村镇发现
- Why? - Because we found
另外两具尸体  一样作案手法
two other bodies in Little Village, same M.O.
所以我们找的可能是同一个人
So we're probably looking for the same guy.
我们目前唯一线索是死者说过
The only lead we got is the DOA said some gangbanger
黑帮成员威胁了他
was threatening him.
我们让他过来  填一个官方报告
We told him to come in, file an official report,
但他第二天就死了
but he got killed the next day.
知道那个黑帮成员的名字吗
Do you have this gangbanger's name?
只有外号  Q
Only his nickname: Q.
-你线人那有消息吗  -有
- Any word back from your CI? - Yeah.
生意目前搁置了
The deal is on ice for now.
君主帮现在很警觉
Kings are on high-alert.
那两个宣誓者惹的祸让他们很紧张
Those two pledges getting whacked made them nervous.
关于这个黑帮成员Q有情报吗
We got any intel on this gangbanger Q?
警长  他的名字几天前在监听中出现了
Yeah, Sarge, his name came up on the wire a few days ago.
原话是"让Q去送枪
Exact quote was "Have Q deliver the guns.
放在22号的桌球馆  老价格"
Drop off at the pool hall on 22nd. Usual price."
我猜是小村镇的什么地方
I'm assuming that's somewhere in Little Village?
22号有这么一个地方叫凯德斯桌球馆
There's this place called Kedzie Billiards on 22nd.
可能是Q常去的地方
Could be Q's hangout.
好  你俩去查查
All right, check it out, you two.
芝加哥警署  我们找一个叫Q的人
CPD. We're looking for a guy named Q.
-有什么好笑  -不  我就是一乐
- Something funny? - No, I'm just happy.
这难道也违法了吗
There's no law against that, is there?
不  但对警察撒谎就违法了
No, but there's a law against lying to the cops
所以你可能要再考虑下回答
so maybe you want to rethink your answer.
我发誓不知道叫Q的人
I swear to God on my mother I don't know a man named Q.
打扰了
Excuse me.
我们在找一个叫Q的人
We're looking for someone named Q.
也许你能帮到我们
Maybe you could help us out?
不知道那个名字
Don't know no one by that name.
是吗  你胳膊上是什么
Really? What's that on your arm?
我们要让你去一趟警局
We're gonna need to take you down to the District,
问你几个问题
ask you a few questions.
关于什么
About what?
三个死掉的强奸犯
Three dead rapists.
你知道米格尔·斯拉泽吗
Do you know Miguel Salazar?
不
No.
爱德华多·瓦格斯呢
What about Eduardo Vargas?
-不认识  -这两位男士
- Mm-mm. - These two fine gentlemen
性侵了两个女孩
sexually assaulted two girls.
杀了一个  还有一个逃跑了
Killed one. The other one got away.
和我有什么关系
What's that got to do with me?
我们只想知道你是否认识这两人
We just want to know if you know these two guys.
两个强奸犯
Two rapists.
我已经说了不知道
And I already told you no.
蒂娜·瓦斯克斯呢  认识吗
What about Tina Vasquez? You know her?
她的住处仅离你几个街区
See, she only lives a few blocks from you.
很多人的住处都离你几个街区
Lots of folks live a few blocks from me.
大多数人看到这个都会吓一跳
Most people cringe at something like that.
我不是大多数人
I ain't most people.
是啊
Yeah.
你不是
You're not.
你厉害多了
You're tougher.
更无所畏惧
More fearless.
因为你为朋友而战
'Cause you stand up for your friends.
为女性  还有年轻女孩
For women, for young girls.
所以有人强奸了女性  你就杀了他们
And then when someone commits a rape, you kill 'em
然后阉了他们
and you castrate them.
要问我  我觉得你值得嘉奖
You ask me, you deserve a trophy.
但这不是解决问题的方式
But that's not the way the world works.
说完了吗
You done?
我现在可以走了吗
Can I go now?
伊莎贝尔·托里斯  外号Q
伊莎贝尔·托里斯  外号Q  皇后的简称
Isabel Torres, street name Q. Short for Queen.
一串犯罪纪录  毒品  盗窃  严重伤害罪
Long rap sheet: drugs, larceny, aggravated assault.
她有一个全女性帮派  叫毒蛇天后
She runs an all-female gang called the Viper Queens,
但大多数时候  他们为当地男性帮派
but for the most part, they're a delivery service
-送货  -是啊  让女性做这种事
- for the local male gangs. - Yeah, woman behind the wheel
会让被捕风险减少一半  或者60%
lowers the risk of arrest by 50%, maybe 60%.
是啊  不管中不中听  我们都被偏见
Yeah, because like it or not, we're all biased.
我们不把女性归为罪犯
We don't profile women as criminals.
她们不够强壮  不够强硬
They're not strong enough, they're not tough enough.
这话有些过了吧
That's a little bit of an overstatement.
是吗
Really?
因为我们谈起案子里的嫌犯时
Because we never used "Her" or "She"
从不说"她"
when talking about suspects in this case.
从最开始就说"他"
It was "He" and "Him" from the jump.
-有道理  -别争了
- She kind of makes a point. - Okay, enough.
我们有个凶杀案要查
We got homicides to solve.
现在  我们一点头绪都没
Right now, we got a whole lot of nothing.
没有物证  没有鉴证科的证据
No physical evidence, no forensics.
所以查查这些强奸案受害者
So dig into these rape victims.
找找她们和这个女性帮主Q的联系
Find the connection with this female banger Q.
你们剩下的人  走访邻里
Rest of you, canvas the neighborhood
了解这些帮派成员出现的地方
where the bangers got popped.
给他们看Q的照片
Show photos of them, Q.
也许有人在案发时间附近见过她们
Maybe someone saw them together near the time of the murders.
警长  我在看法医报告
Hey, Sarge, I'm looking at this M.E. Report,
基于胃部余留物
and based on stomach contents,
看上去君主帮最后吃的食物是披萨
it looks like the last thing the Kings had to eat was pizza.
所以你让我和鲁塞克去查查当地餐馆吧
So you should let me and Ruzek check out some local restaurants.
这是个开始调查的好地方
Well, there's a good place to start.
对  见过他
Yeah, I've seen him before.
他们经常来  其中一人
They come here a lot. One of them...
这个人
That one.
欠我5块
Owes me $5.
你得把这钱记成无法收回了
You might want to write that off as uncollectible.
-他死了  -对  都死了
- He's dead. - Yeah, they both are.
-他们才来过  -和她一起吗
- They were just here. - Were they with her?
不
No.
但和一个女孩来的  很漂亮的女孩
But they were with a girl. She was real pretty, too.
能形容下外表吗
All right, can you describe her for me?
拉丁裔
Uh, she's Latina.
金色卷发
Blondish hair. Curly.
苗条但不是很瘦  如果你明白我的意思
She was thin but not too thin if you know what I mean.
明白  继续
Sure, keep going.
中等个头
She was medium height.
很漂亮的棕色眼睛
And she had real pretty brown eyes.
-听起来好美啊  -是啊
- She sounds fine as hell. - Yeah.
但我不想听上去像个变态
But I didn't want to sound like a creeper, you know?
-是啊  -听着
- Oh, yeah. - All right, hey, listen.
我们得看一下你们的监控录像
We need to look at your surveillance video.
你认识这姑娘吗
So you know who this girl is?
认识  维罗妮卡
Yeah, yeah, that's Veronica.
她和那个叫Q的姑娘以前经常和君主帮打交道
She and that girl Q used to run with the Kings.
但他们在潘尼亚坐牢的时候扩张了
But they branched out when Peña was up in Stateville.
扩展成了某种女性团体
Some sort of chick-clique.
全是女孩  叫毒蛇天后
All girls. Viper Queens.
那些小婊子们也不是开玩笑的
Them bitches don't play, neither.
特别是Q
Especially Q.
-好吧  -她是个铁石心肠的杀手
- Okay. - She a stone-cold killer.
跟我们讲讲维罗妮卡  她的专长是什么
Talk to us about Veronica. What's her specialty?
运毒  和君主帮合作
Drug runs. Works with the Kings.
还有很多南边的黑人帮派
And lots of black gangs on the South Side.
好  我需要你今天和她交易
All right, I need you to do a deal with her today.
3块
Three bricks.
我们怎么在这么短的时间找到这么多货啊  兄弟
How we gonna find that kind of weight on short notice, man?
商店
The grocery store.
小苏打和维生素B
Baking soda and Vitamin B.
放轻松  兄弟
Take it easy, man.
安东尼奥的线人说是三点  是吗
Antonio's CI said 3:00, right?
是  也就是说五六点  如果我们走运的话
Yeah, which means 5:00, maybe 6:00 if we're lucky.
如果你想守时的话  不要和线人约会
if you're looking for punctuality, don't date a CI.
或意大利人
Or an Italian.
我以前和一个罗马人约会过
I dated a guy from Rome once.
我知道得越多  越意识到
The more I learn about you, the more I realize
我根本不知道你是个什么样的人
I have no clue who you really are.
很好  要的就是这个效果
Good. My plan is working.
但安东尼奥那里怎么样就不清楚了
Antonio's plan on the other hand, not so sure.
女生是很难策反的
Girls are tough to flip.
-比男生难  -难得多
- Tougher than boys? - Way tougher.
所以女性比男性要更忠诚
So women are more loyal than men?
当然
Absolutely.
看来这就是我们要找的姑娘了
Looks like this is our girl.
她拿走了背包和钱  行动
She's got the backpack and the money, let's roll.
我们绕后
We'll take the back.
好
Yeah.
门是开的
It's open.
-准备完毕  你准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready, you ready? - Yep.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
举起手来
Get your hands up!
把手放在我能看见的地方
Hands where I can see them.
-朝墙站好  -你的背包呢
- Here against the wall. - Where's your backpack?
-什么背包  -你的背包呢
- What backpack? - Where's your backpack?
-什么在哪  -搞定她了吗
- Where's what? - Got her?
把手放在我能看到的地方
Keep your hands where I can see them.
好了  你们俩  过来
All right, you too, over here.
靠墙站着  别动
Stay against the wall. Don't move.
-是厄普顿  -好
- Upton's coming out! - Okay.
没有背包  她把背包给了某个人
No backpack. She passed it off to someone.
那里
There!
5021C  注意  两位便衣警察
5021 Charlie, be advised, two plainclothes officers
在追一名穿着黑色夹克  背着红背包的女性
are in pursuit of a female, red backpack, black jacket.
-下来  让开  -别挡道
- Get down! Get down! - Move out of the way!
-靠墙站着  -让开
- Stay to the wall! - Get out of the way!
警察  让开  让开  让开
Police! Move, move, move!
-警察  -停  停
- Police! - Halt, halt!
-我从右边走  -好
- I'm going right. - Got you.
靠边  让开  让开  让开  让开
Straight on the wall! Move, move, move, move!
停下  停下  芝加哥警察
Stop, stop! Chicago PD!
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
让开
Move out of the way!
让开  让开  让开  让开
Move, move, move, move!
-别动  -停下
- Freeze! - Stop right there.
-举起手来  -不许动
- Hands up! - Do not move!
结束了  把背包放下
It is over. Put the backpack down.
把背包放下
Put the backpack down.
转过身来
Turn around.
蒂娜
Tina.
我们看到了转手过程  维罗妮卡
We saw the handoff, Veronica.
一个男的停车  给了你一个信封
A man pulled up, gave you an envelope,
然后给了你一个红色背包
and then handed you a red backpack.
里面有一批货
It had a bunch of coke inside it.
我以为那是学习用品
I thought it was school supplies.
你可看了好一阵
You're staring down some real time here.
-无话可说  -是吗
- Got nothing to say. - Yeah?
那对于这个你有话可说吗
You have something to say about this?
看一看吧
Why don't you take a look?
据我们所知  你是个诱饵
Way we heard it, you were the bait.
你和那些家伙在披萨店见面
You met up with the pledges at the pizza joint,
你和他们玩了一会
you played with 'em a little bit,
然后你就回到他们的房子里
and then you went back to their house
让Q进去
where you let Q inside.
她收拾了他们  然后把他们阉了
She whacks them then castrates them.
我永远都不会背叛Q的
I ain't never gonna switch up on Q.
她是我的人
She's my girl.
我的姐妹
My sister.
所以你可以省省了
So y'all can stop doing the dance.
好吧
Okay.
但是总得有人为他们的谋杀案负责
But someone's got to pay the ticket for those murders
所以如果你不说的话
so if you're not going to talk
那就得由你来背锅了
then that someone's gonna be you.
那起诉我吧
So charge me.
就知道你们在诈我
Knew you was bluffin'.
我能走了吗
Am I free to go?
你想怎么做  警长
What do you want to do, Sarge?
因为我们不能因为运送
'Cause we can't charge her on distribution
维生素B和小苏打起诉她
of Vitamin B and baking soda.
放她走
Kick her.
我们还有另一个孩子
We still got this other kid.
她不知道那是假毒品
She has idea it's fake coke.
也许可以诈住她
Maybe this little trick will work with her.
等等
Wait.
-你们觉得是我干的  -运毒的是你
- You think I did that? - Well, you're running drugs.
谁知道呢  也许谋杀案也是你干的
Who knows, maybe you're doing murders, too.
不  不  我不会那么做的
No, no. I could never do that.
你觉得运毒不是什么问题
You didn't have a problem running coke.
我也不想  我...
I didn't want to. I...
-我别无选择  -什么意思
- I didn't have a choice. - What do you mean?
蒂娜  是你让Q杀了那两个男孩的吗
Tina, did you ask Q to kill those two boys?
我很害怕
I was scared.
我觉得他们会找到我  杀了我
I thought they were gonna come find me and kill me.
所以我给我表亲打了电话
So I called my cousin.
她在混黑帮
She's in the gang.
让我去跟Q谈
Told me to talk to Q.
说她可以保护我
Said that she could help protect me.
很好
Good.
没关系的  没关系
It's okay. It's good.
你只是想保护自己
You were just protecting yourself.
现在我们可以帮你解决这事  好吗
Now we can help you make this go away, okay?
但你得帮忙
But you have to help us.
抱歉
Sorry.
这个里面有摄像头吗
This has a camera inside it?
是的  所以我们什么都能听到看到
Yeah, so we'll be able to see and hear everything.
但你别把玩也别碰它
But don't play with it or touch it
不然你可能会紧张
'cause that might make you nervous.
记住  我们需要她承认杀了人
Remember, we need her to confess to the murders.
你要想办法让她说出
You find a way to get her to talk about
在那房子里发生的事
what happened in that house.
对  但不要逼得太紧
Yeah, but don't push too hard.
记住  我就在外面
Look, remember, I'm gonna be right outside.
我们都在外面
We're all gonna be right outside
所以不管发生任何事我们都会出现
so if anything happens we'll be right there.
这是霍斯特德警探和阿普顿警探
This is Detective Halstead and Upton.
你准备好了吗  我们要带你回小村镇了
You all set? We're gonna take you back to Little Village.
走吧
Come on.
那之后呢
And then what happens?
你走去Q家
You're gonna walk over to Q's house
然后跟她说警察把你带进警局
and you're gonna tell her that the cops brought you in.
他们问了你很多问题
They asked you a lot of questions
但你什么都没有告诉他们
but you didn't tell them anything.
而且他们没有证据
And they didn't have any evidence
因为你被带走之前把背包藏起来了
because you stashed the backpack before you got pinched.
好的
Okay.
好  开始了  她要进屋了
Okay, here we go. She's stepping to the house.
我希望这孩子能成功
I hope this kid can pull it off.
好  进来吧
All right, come on.
你还背着背包
You still have the backpack.
他们抓我之前我把它藏到柜子里了
I hid it in a locker before they could arrest me.
锁上之后就没人能找到
Closed the door so no one could find it.
聪明  很聪明
That was smart. Real smart.
谢谢
Thanks.
所以警察就这么放你走了吗
So the police, they just let you go?
是的
Yeah.
他们说什么了
What did they say?
他们问了你什么
What kind of questions did they ask you?
他们想知道毒品在哪儿
They wanted to know where the drugs were,
谁给我的  还有我怎么认识维罗妮卡的
who gave them to me, and how I knew Veronica.
你怎么说
And what did you say?
我说我不知道什么毒品
I said that I didn't know about any drugs,
维罗妮卡是我的邻居
and that I knew Veronica from the neighborhood.
不错
That's good.
很好
Bueno.
你真的应该为自己感到骄傲
You should feel really proud of yourself.
第一次被调查  你的表现很专业
You handled your first bust like a pro.
那为什么我感觉这么...糟糕
Then how come I feel so...awful?
你经历了很多事情  T
You've been through a lot, T.
那些人对你和你朋友做的事...
What those guys did to you and your friend...
需要用时间冲淡
It takes time to get over.
相信我  我知道
Trust me, I know.
-你是说  -是的
- You saying that-- - Yes.
我也经历过
It happened to me too.
那时我14岁
I was 14.
所以你才对那两个人那样
So that's why you did what you did to those guys.
是的
I did that.
我杀他们是因为我想保护你们
I killed them because I wanted to protect you.
还有其她潜在的受害人
And other future victims.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
都不许动
Nobody move!
-手  -转过去
- Hands! - Turn around.
你真让我恶心
You make me sick.
蒂娜安排好了吗
Tina all set?
是的  她在去机场的路上
Yeah, she's on the way to the airport.
她去跟她姑姑住一段时间
She's gonna live with her aunt for a while.
很好  我把Q关起来了
Good. All right, I got Q in the box.
你去让她认罪
I want you to get her confession.
把这案子定下来
Let's put this thing to bed.
我想跟她做个交易
I want to offer her a deal.
交易  你开什么玩笑
A deal? You got to be kidding me.
这女人手上我们知道的就有三条人命
This woman's got three bodies to her name that we know of.
明白  但她杀的又不是乖孩子
Understood, but it's not like she's killing choir boys.
她杀的是禽兽
She's killing monsters.
她在帮那些走投无路的女孩
She's helping girls with nowhere to turn
她们不敢报警
who are afraid to talk to the police.
-她在帮她们  警长  -金  金
- She is helping them, Sergeant. - Kim. Kim.
不管怎样都没用
Either way it doesn't mean a damn thing
除非她能给到我们想要的东西
unless she's got something to give us that we want.
-比如潘尼亚  -是的
- Like Peña? - Well, yeah.
那挺好  但他的人都按兵不动了
That would be good, but his entire crew is on lock down.
我们也想做交易
Been trying to set up a deal.
Q和潘尼亚以前在一个帮派
Q and Peña used to run in the same gang.
他们认识
They know each other.
我觉得我可以让她加入
I think I can get her to play ball.
值得一试
It's worth a shot.
叫上阿普顿跟你一起
Grab Upton and get your play together.
好的
Yeah.
是的
I did that.
我杀他们是因为我想保护你们
I killed them because I wanted to protect you.
所以  这是你
So, that's you
承认了双重谋杀
admitting to a double murder.
我们知道你为什么杀那些人
Look, we know why you killed those guys.
在某种程度上我们明白
And on some level we get it.
所以我们想要跟你做个交易
Which is why we're willing to offer you a deal.
不做  我不会出卖我的姑娘
Hell no. I'm not snitching on my girls.
好的
That's okay.
因为我们想的要是荷西·潘尼亚
Because we want Jorge Peña.
是的
Yeah.
你能拿下他吗
Can you get him?
可以
Yeah.
简单
That's easy.
所以你会配合吗  戴窃听器
So you'll cooperate? You'll wear a wire?
可以
Yeah.
你们别去找其她姑娘就行
You just leave the rest of my girls alone.
她们跟这事无关
They ain't got nothing to do with this.
我一个人开的枪  一个人割的
I did all the shooting. I did all the cutting.
都是我干的
It was all me.
成交
Deal.
Q试探了潘尼亚
Q put a feeler out to Peña.
他有兴趣买一批枪  所以行动成了
He's interested in buying some guns, so it's a go.
-我们只需要一台"游戏机"  -干什么
- All we need is a gaming console. - For what?
Q通过这个跟大玩家和其它成员谈条件
It's how Q sets up terms with big players and other crews,
好让大家都远离警方视线
that way everyone stays off the radar.
那就找个游戏什么
So grab one of these gaming things.
我们开始行动
Let's get this operation moving.
汉克
Hank.
既然那个帮派小妞认罪了
Since that gang chick confessed,
那我就回重案组了
I think I'm gonna head back to Homicide.
-跟伯吉斯合作如何  -很好
- How'd it go with Burgess? - Great.
她很专业
She's a real pro.
-谢谢帮忙  -不客气
- Thanks for the help. - You got it.
看起来不错
Looks good.
请伸出左手腕
Let me see your left wrist, please.
接起来  里面是窃听器
Throw this on. It's a wire in that, okay?
好了  告诉你一声
All right, just so you know,
车上有定位追踪器
there's a GPS tracker on the car.
还有关闭开关  所有武器的
There's a kill switch and the firing pins
开火开关也都拿掉了
have been removed from the weapons
所以你不要动歪心眼
so don't get any crazy ideas.
不用担心
Ain't nothing to worry about.
都是生意
I'm all about business.
这次行动成功  你只用坐15年牢
You play this right, you'll do 15 instead of life.
考虑到你的罪状  这很不错了
And that's pretty good considering your resume.
谢谢
I appreciate this.
我不会让你失望
I won't let you down.
我也恨潘尼亚
I hate Peña too.
好
Yeah.
如果你不介意我问
Hey, if you don't mind me asking...
-什么  -你姐姐现在怎么样
- Yeah? - How's your sister doing?
不太好
Not so good.
她在努力
I mean, she's trying.
但总得有个过程
She is, but it's a process.
一个漫长而复杂的过程
A long, complicated process.
我想陪她
I'm trying to be there for her.
我想支持她  但是
I'm trying to support her, but...
好像我越努力  她就越推开我
It's like the more I try, the more she pushes me away.
那些把她害成这样的混蛋
And those bastards that did this to her
在里面待个
are gonna be out in...
一年就出来
Like a year?
-去喝酒  -她来了
- Going to happy hour... - Here she comes.
那是什么
What the hell was that?
不知道  红色轿车停下
I-I don't know, the red sedan pulled up
司机给了Q什么东西
and the driver passed something to Q.
-是枪吗  -有可能
- What, a gun? - It could be.
她在不在这里都不一定
How does anyone even know that she's here?
不知道  可能是"游戏机"
I don't know, the gaming console, maybe?
我们得上报  得告诉博伊特
We gotta call this in. We gotta tell Voigt.
海莉  这是抓到潘尼亚的最好机会
Hailey, this is our best chance to get Pena.
金  上报
Kim, call it in!
好  注意  潘尼亚的车
All right, be advised, we got Peña's car
正在接近目标位置
approaching target location.
你不上报我上报了
Call it in or I will.
警长  一辆车停下给了Q什么东西
Sarge, a car pulled up and passed Q something.
什么
What are you saying?
有可能是武器  我没看清楚
It could be a weapon; I could not make it out clearly.
你不确定吗
So you're not sure?
是的
Correct.
好  那我们先静观其变
All right, then let's just play it out.
潘尼亚到了
Peña's arrived.
很高兴你联络我  Q
Glad you reached out, Q.
好久了
It's been a minute.
是啊
Yeah.
但最近我经常想起你
But I've been thinking about you a lot lately.
我只是在等合适的时机联系你
I was just waiting for the right time to connect.
我听说你有些货
So I hear you got some heaters.
是啊  不少呢
Yeah, I got a lot.
有自动机枪
Got some automatics.
九毫米
Some nines.
霰弹枪
Some shotguns.
来复枪
Rifles.
现在行动
Move in now.
你没那个胆子  小姑娘
You ain't got it in you, little girl.
求你
Please.
我没对不起你
I never did you wrong.
放下枪  Q
Drop the gun, Q.
放下
Drop it!
马上
Do it!
很好
Yeah, that's right.
不许动  手放到我看到的地方
Don't move. Hands where I can see 'em.
你搞砸了  Q  真的搞砸了
You blew it, Q. You really blew it.
不  我得偿所愿了
No, I got what I wanted.
强奸我的人就是潘尼亚
Peña's the one who raped me.
夺回控制权的感觉真是再好不过了
Ain't nothing feel better than taking back the power.
走
Come on.
好  明早我会把文件放到你的办公桌上
Yes, sir, I will have the file on your desk in the morning.
我跟副局长通过已经
And I have been on the phone with the deputy chief
-一个小时了  -我知道那是把枪
- for the last hour- - I knew it was a gun.
我看到了  警长
I saw it, Sarge.
我应该告诉你的  但我没有
I should have told you, but I didn't.
因为我并不关心
Because I didn't really care...
Q是不是杀死那个混蛋
if Q killed that son of a bitch.
坐
Have a seat.
-坐  好
- Sit down. - Okay.
其实不止那样  警长
Actually it's more than that, Sarge.
我有点想让她那么做
I kind of wanted her to do it.
我想让她杀了那头猪
Like, I wanted her to kill that pig.
让他为自己造成的痛苦付出代价
Make him pay for all the pain he caused.
我想要那样
I wanted that.
算了
Well...
不管有没有看到枪
Gun or no gun.
都不重要了
Doesn't really matter.
因为
Because...
我不会让任何人妨碍那次行动
I wasn't gonna let anybody kill that operation.
要我说
You ask me...
没有荷西·潘尼亚的芝加哥更美好
Chicago is a better place with Jorge Peña dead.
放下吧
Let it go.